[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city was movie character Forrest Gump born and raised in?", "correct_answer": "Greenbow, Alabama", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackson, Mississippi", "Greenville, Alabama", "Cleveland, Alabama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In  Transformers 2, what is the name of the blue Chevrolet Volt (with the pair of electric whips)?", "correct_answer": "Jolt", "incorrect_answers": ["Hit", "Whip", "Hiss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is always an easy answer to every human problem - neat, plausible and wrong. What sharp and witty American writer made this observation?", "correct_answer": "H.L. Mencken", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry James", "Louisa May Alcott", "James Fenimore Cooper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet of the Solar System is also known as The Evening Star?", "correct_answer": "Venus", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Earth", "Uranus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The medical term cardio, deriving from a Greek word, refers to which organ of the human body?", "correct_answer": "Heart", "incorrect_answers": ["Brain", "Liver", "Lungs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the official language of the Federative Republic of Brazil?", "correct_answer": "Portuguese", "incorrect_answers": ["English and Spanish", "Spanish", "Spanish and Portuguese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest and richest city in Brazil?", "correct_answer": "Sao Paulo", "incorrect_answers": ["Salvador", "Rio de Janeiro", "Brasilia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Princess Protection Program, Carter has a crush on Donny.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Earths atmosphere comprises of which two main elements?", "correct_answer": "Oxygen and Nitrogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Oxygen and Hydrogen", "Hydrogen and Oxone", "Nitrogen and Hydrogen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Otto Lilienthal, the first person to make repeated successful gliding flights, died after an airplane accident on 10 August 1896. What were the last words he uttered moments before he passed away?", "correct_answer": "Sacrifices must be made", "incorrect_answers": ["I am not dying in vain, I am dying in the name of progress", "It was all worth it", "I gave all I had"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The atomic number of Argon is 19.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What place did the Yorkshire Terrier take in the AKC registered breed popularity in the USA in 2008?", "correct_answer": "2nd", "incorrect_answers": ["1st", "50th", "79th"]}]